Alesia Gillespie, RN -

Address: 1239 Compton St. Dallas, TX 75203

Cell:972-201-6741

Email: alesiagl@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE:

To be part of a team that will continue to make me grow as nurse. A place where my experience and knowledge will be an asset. I would be honored be given an opportunity to assist in the care of patients during their surgical experience in the OR as a circulating nurse.

QUALIFICATIONS:

Proficient in general surgeries, plastics, peripheral vascular procedures, bariatrics, ENT, urology, arthroscopies, laparoscopies, minor orthopedics, transplants, neurology, gynecological procedures and endoscopies.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

OR CIRCULATOR RN- First Baptist Medical center Dallas TX; February 2016-Present
OR CIRCULATOR RN- The Micro Surgery Institute Dallas TX; April 2009- February 2016
OR CIRCULATOR/ SCRUB RN- Kindred Hospital Dallas TX; March 2003-March 2009
OR CIRCULATOR/ SCRUB RN- Medical City Dallas TX; June 2001-March 2003
OR CIRCULATOR/ SCRUB RN- Medical Center of Lancaster TX; November 1999-June 2001

EDUCATION:

- El Centro College Dallas Texas-Associate of Art and Science Graduated in June 1993
- El Centro College- Dallas Texas- Surgical Technology- Graduated in June 1994
- El Centro College- Dallas Texas- Associate of Applied Science in Nursing-Graduated June 2009

SKILLS:

I have worked in several surgical settings and thus acquired great adaptability, self-motivation, ability to work under pressure, communication and decision-making skills. I am a great team player and consider myself an everyday learner.

References available upon request